字幕转制｜天外生物
感谢原字幕制作者
人与机器之间的界限在未来将会消失
先进的技术允许人类使用义体 强化智能
阪华机械是一间由政府出资用来打击高科技犯罪的公司
将人类大脑植入机器人体内 开发出具有人类
智慧及钢铁身躯全身义体强化的军事特务
[研究代号 二五七一]
氧气含量下降
Decrease of oxygen content
脑功能正常
Normal brain function
马上进行移植
Transplant right away
准备装上机器人骨架
Ready to install the skeleton of a robot
启动二五七一研究计划
Start the 2571 research program
攻壳机动队
现在你可以睁眼了
Now you can open your eyes
你很安全
You are safe.
没事的 深呼吸
It's ok, just breathe.
大口呼吸
Just breathe.
呼吸
Breathe.
很好
Good.
非常好
That's good.
嗨 蜜拉
Hello Mia.
我是欧莱特博士
I'm Dr... Ouelet.
你还记得你遭遇袭击的事吗
Do you remember anything about the attack?
发生了什么事
What happened?
我掉到水里了
I was... You were drowning.
那里有水
There was water.
没错 你在一艘难民船上
That's right. You were on a boat, a refugee boat.
被恐怖分子击沉
It was sank by terrorists.
为什么我的身体没有知觉
Why can't I feel my body?
你的身体受创严重 我们救不了她
Mira, your body was damaged. We could not save that.
但你的大脑是好的
Only your brain survived.
所以我们做了一个新的身体
We made you a new body.
和你的大脑接在一起
A synthetic shell.
你的思想 你的记忆
But your mind, your soul...
甚至于你的灵魂
Your ghost.
依然存在
It's still in there.
请帮她
Please.
冷静下来
Sedate her.
这样没问题吗
Will it work?
绝对可以的
Absolutely.
她是一个奇迹
She's a miracle.
机器不能思考 只会服从命令
A machine can't lead, It can only follow orders.
机器没有感情 想像力 同情心
A machine can't imagine or care or intuit.
但有了人类的大脑来控制它
But as a human mind in a cybernetic frame...
就能弥补这些不足 甚至做的更多
Mira can do all those things, and more.
这是第一个成功的作品
The first of her kind.
一旦开始运作 她将被指派到公安九课
She will join Section 9 as soon as she is operational.
请不要这么做
Please don't do that.
不要把复杂的人类大脑 简化成一台机器
You reducing a complex human to a machine.
我不认为她是一台机器
I don't think of her as a machine.
她是一个武器
She is a weapon.
也是我们公司的未来
And the future of my company.
[一年后]
赛恩训练协助是开发你的潜能
The first artificially created memory enhancement.
最快和最有效的方式
Sirenum training protocol is the fastest and most efficient way...
提升你的智力
to develop your ability.
比以前更强大 体验你的力量
Stronger than ever. Experience your power.
网络犯罪已列为重大刑案 最低本刑十五年以上
Cybercrime is a Type 1 offense. Minimum punishment: 15 years in prison.
阪华机械保障你的人身安全
Hanka Robotics guarantees personal safety against.
全员注意 第十三区发现网路犯罪活动
All patrolling area units, be advised possible cybercrime activity in vicinity.
邻近空域即将关闭
Airspace in adjoining areas will be locked down.
公安九课已抵达现场
Section 9 is currently on site.
重复 第十三区发现网路犯罪活动
I repeat: All patrolling area units, be advised, possible cyber crime...
我是少校 我已就位
This is major. I'm on site.
等待指示
Awaiting instructions.
分析与报告
Analyze and report.
我是人类 我有缺陷
I'm human, I am flawed.
但是我接受改变义体强化手术
But I embrace change...
在我装了电子脑之后
and enhancement.
如今我无所不能
Now there is nothing I can't do.
无所不知 无所不在
Nothing I can't know, nothing I can't be.
我要你听一听这个
Wait and listen to something.
那是我四岁女儿的歌声
It's my 4 year old daughter.
她在唱摇篮曲时
In the time it took her to sing that lullaby
也学会说流利的法语
she learned to speak fluent French.
你们知道那首歌…
Do you know that song...?
这里有一个回迹箱
There is an echo box up here.
有人在扫描资料传送
Someone is scanning data traffic.
把他找出来
Keeps track of where it is transmitted.
先让我看看他在扫描谁
To see who's worth this kind of surveillance.
连接酒店内部保安网路
Accessing hotel security network.
给点提示 课长 这里有太多的资讯
What're you seeing, sir? I've got a lot of hotel to scan.
看看非洲联邦总统所在的宴会厅 阪华商务会议
There is a banquet room reserved for the President of the African Federation.
邀请人是奥斯蒙博士 他是阪华机械的顾问
Dr. Osmond is invited on behalf of Hanka Robotics.
有了 四十三楼
Got it. 43rd floor.
派人通知总统的幕僚 告诉他有人在监视他
Someone contacted the president staff. Someone is watching him.
奥斯蒙博士
Dr. Osmond...
你要我们为你做什么
What is it you want from us?
你应该问阪华机械能为你做什么
I think it is more about what Hanka Robotics can do for you.
全球七成三的人口 早已进入义体强化时代
73% of this world has woken up to the age of cyber enhancement.
你不怕跟不上时代吗
Do you really wanna be left behind?
我的人民欢迎义体强化 我也一样
My people embrace cyber enhancement as do I.
但是没有人知道 操弄人类灵魂
There is no one who really understand the risk...
对自我身分认同所造成的危险
To individuality, identity, messing with the human soul.
各位 抱歉 你们走错房间…
Gentlemen, Excuse me, I think you've the wrong...
走廊发生枪击 六名男子闯入
Hallway. Six men. Shots fired.
九课队员多久会到
Section 9 ETA?
两分钟到达 少校
Two minutes out, Major.
太久了 我要进去
Too long. I'm going in.
等一下
Hold!
少校 留在原地
Mayor, stop!
你们的竞争对手也说过同样的话
I had heard this speech before from your competitors.
而现在 阪华机械却用劣酒招待我们
And now Hanka Robotics serves it with Milky suck.
你在做什么
What are you doing
你看 我就怕会变成这样
Look. This is what I'm talking about.
少校
Mayor!
开始入侵 撷取资讯
Initiate... The hack.
救救我 拜托 别让我死
Help me. Please. Don't let me die.
是谁派你来的
Who sent you?
救救我 求求你
Help me. Please.
回答我
Answer me!
谁跟阪华机械同流合污 谁就得死
Collaborates with Hanka Robotics will be destroyed.
你还好吗
You okay?
你受伤了
You're injured.
你跟她不一样
You're not the same.
嘿
Hey.
她只是个机器人
It's just a robot!
[小南瓜 - 记忆残影]
[使用大脑移植抗排斥的药物]
你的皮肤应该更好 试试我们的护肤霜
Your skin deserves the best, so do you. Try our hand cream.
[国防部中央办公室第九区]
我们究竟了解奥斯蒙博士多少
So what do we have on Osmond?
到目前为止 不多
So far, very little.
他是阪华机械的顾问
He was the head of Hanka's robotics division.
是人类 但装了电子脑义体强化
Human, but of course cyber enhanced.
他是如何被入侵的
So how did they hack him?
那批艺妓机器人破解了他的加密
Somehow this geisha bot got past his encryption.
你有点不一样
Something is different.
义体强化哪里了
What'd you get?
为什么你一直认为他有强化
Why you always thinking he's out there enhancing.
因为他就是做了
Because he is.
电子机器肝
A cyber mech liver.
我存了很久的钱
Been saving up for a while.
以后想喝多少都没问题
Now it's lost cool every night.
你义体强化 就只是为了贪杯
You got enhanced so you can drink more?
没有义体强化就没有我们 德古沙
Embrace enhancements, Togusa. We would not be here without it.
我很高兴我没做义体强化
I am all human and happy, thanks.
那批艺妓机器人怎么样了
Any more information about the seized geisha bot?
阪华机械正在检查
Hanka is running scans.
达林博士稍晚会有报告
Dr. Dahlin will have the reports ready but...
我刚刚跟总理见面
I've been talking to the Prime Minister.
他想要一份完整的报告
He wants a full report.
德古沙
Togusa.
昨晚的袭击事件后
Following last night's attack...
阪华机械又有三位科学家遇害
3 more Hanka's scientists were murdered...
就在他们的中央实验室
in the company's central laboratory.
前两个是枪杀
The first two were shot...
第三个被活活打死 凶手是他的机器人
and the third was beaten to death by his own service robot.
他们的大脑都被入侵过
All showed signs of cerebral hacking.
跟奥斯蒙一样的手法
The same as the geisha did to Osmond.
他们都是阪华机械的高层
And all were senior figures... in Hanka.
就像奥斯蒙博士
Just like Osmond.
每个犯罪现场 都留下一条讯息
A message was left at each of the crime scene...
留下讯息的人自称
By someone identifying himself...
九世
as Kuze.
谁跟阪华机械同流合污 谁就得死
Collaborate with Hanka Robotics should be destroyed.
谁跟阪华机械同流合污
Collaborate with Hanka Robotics...
谁就得死
should be destroyed.
德古沙
Togusa.
你去找阪华机械的社长卡特了解一下
You and Ladriya go speak to Mr. Cutter, the CEO of Hanka.
少校跟巴特 去找达林博士要报告
Major and Batou take a look at Dahlin report.
看到底是谁在幕后搞鬼
Find out what has been recovered from the geisha.
少校
Major!
我叫你先不要行动
I told you not jump off.
我不能等 不然会死更多人
I had to, or more would have died.
你是我们团队的一员 就必须服从命令
You are a member of my team, and my responsibility
我会找到他 并杀了他
I'll find him... and I will kill him.
这是我的任务对不对 课长
It's what I am built for, isn't it?
你不仅仅是一个杀人机器
You are more than just a weapon.
你有灵魂 能思考
You have a soul, a ghost.
这是我们独有的美德
When we see our uniqueness as a virtue...
只有人性 才能为我们带来和平
Only then will we find peace.
安全地重组你宝贝孩子的基因
Safely reconfiguring the child's genetic Structure.
创造更美好的家庭
Families built better.
昨晚在酒店里 你怎么突然跑掉了
What was going on with you at the hotel last night?
我没事
Nothing. I'm fine.
你确定
Are you sure?
- 嘿 美女 要不要升级强化一下  - 滚
- Hey, sweetheart, want an upgrade?  - Move.
- 你想要的我们都有  - 滚开
- I have anything you want.  - Back off!
嘿 明
Hey, Ming!
嘿 巴特
Hey, Batou!
- 你要的骨头  - 谢了兄弟
- Got your bones.  - Thanks man.
那是什么 喂狗吃的
For the dogs.
你连人都不喜欢 怎么会喜欢狗
For someone who doesn't like people How come you care about dogs so much
我喜欢流浪狗 它们也喜欢我
I dont know. I like just strays and they like me.
那是因为你喂它们
They like you Because you feed them.
说这种话
You got no heart.
姑娘们
Hey, girls!
嘿 加布里
Hey Gabriel!
这是少校
Meet Major.
少校 加布里
Major, Gabriel.
我们家养过狗
We used to have a dog.
真的吗
Sure is that?
我还以为你更喜欢猫呢
...more of a cat person.
你从来不提起你的过去
You don't talk about that stuff.
什么
What?
- 你的过去  - 我记得不多
- Your past.  - I don't remember much.
只有一些零星的记忆
Just fragments, bits and pieces.
你的家人呢
What about family?
我的父母带我到这个国家 他们就死了
My parents, they died bringing us to this country.
我们的船被击沉在港口
Our boat sank in the harbor.
我差点淹死
I almost drowned.
我总是觉得
I feel sinking...
有一层浓雾 遮住了我的记忆
there is always this thick fog over my memory.
始终看不清楚
And I can't seen through it.
你很幸运
You are lucky.
我每天每夜都被记忆折磨着
Every single day I get screwed upon my memory.
不记得更好
It's better to be pure.
就像你一样
Like you.
[不法之地 - 记忆残影]
[阪华机械总部]
欢迎光临阪华机械
Welcome to Hanka Robotics.
所有访客必须佩带电子通行证
All visitors must display appropriate credentials at all times.
请把手放开再握紧
Opens and close, please.
你是首屈一指的 但你不是毫无破绽
Your have damaged internal systems.
或许下次你可以把我设计的更好
Maybe next time you can design me better.
- 你好吗  - 我没事 不觉得疼痛
- How are you?  - I am fine. I can't feel anything.
不是的 我是指精神方面
No you, in There.
经常出现幻觉
I have been having glitches...
没多久就消失了
but it will pass.
- 你有按时吃药吗  - 是的
- Have you been taking your medication?  - Yeah.
但是没有用 今天早上又发生二次
But these wounds are so cycling. I had two this morning.
- 声音还是画面  - 都有
- Sound or image?  - Both.
找到了
I see it.
发现未加密的文件 是你下载的吗
You made any unencrypted downloads?
- 不是 请你帮我删除  - 确认删除
- No. Just delete them from me.  - Consent?
我是蜜拉少校 我同意删除这些数据
My name is Major Mary Killian. I give my consent to delete this data.
好了
It's done.
- 让我看看你的脖子  - 那是什么
- No big deal.  - What are they?
是记忆的感官回波 还是幻觉
Sensory echoes from your mind, shadows.
我还不能确定
I'm not sure.
要怎么分辨幻觉跟记忆
How do you know it's a glitch of what's me?
幻觉和你真正的记忆
The glitches have a different texture...
有不同的特征
to the rest of your code.
我什么都看得见
I can see everything.
你的思想 你的决定
All of your thoughts, your... decisions.
看来只有人类才能保有隐私
I guess privacy is just for humans.
你就是人类
You are human.
大家都把你当做人类
People see you as human.
我身边的每个人
Everyone around me seems to fit.
他们好像都有牵挂的事物
They seem connected to something. Something I...
可是我没有
am not...
- 就像我没有过去  - 你当然有过去
- Like I have no past.  - Of course you have a past.
你将会感受和人的羁绊 并关心他们
And at time you'll feel more more connected to it and to them.
手放开再握紧
Opens and close, please.
我们执着于记忆 好像它定义了我们
We cling to memories as if they define us, but...
并非如此
They really don't.
定义我们的是我们的行为
What we do is what defines us.
这里是阪华机械安全管制区 非授权人员请勿进入
You're entering a Hanka secure area. Authorized personal only.
请关闭通信装置
Please disable communication enhancement.
我现在没空
I'm busy.
达林博士 有结果了吗
Dr... Dahlin! Are you finished yet?
如果她没被打的那么惨
If you hadn't rained all the Geisha with the bullets,
那就容易多了
This would be much easier.
- 不是我打的  - 是我
- I didn't shoot him.  - I did.
还要好几天
This is gonna take days.
几百种模拟运算等着我做呢
I need to run hundreds of potential simulations.
我们没有时间了
We don't have the time.
她本来是一个伴侣机器人
She was a Hanka companion bot.
但被入侵 重新修改程式
But she was reprogrammed for cerebral hacking.
硬碟检查过了吗
What was on her drives?
没有东西 数据在入侵完就被删除了
Nothing. The data was destroyed as it was transmitted.
查不出他想偷什么
No sign of what she was up to.
硬件遭到破坏
The hardware was vandalized.
破坏的很彻底
They ripped her up.
那我得深潜找到被删除的档案
Then I have to do a deep dive.
深潜时你无法加密保护自已
You can't encrypt you in the deep dive
我知道
I know it.
对方可能有陷阱 比如电磁波 病毒
They could left traps in her. Mag pulses, viruses.
她说得对
She is right.
你的大脑暴露在敌人眼前 门户大开
You will be exposing your mind to who ever hacked her. You'll be wide open.
我必须要这样做 才能尽快找到九世
I have to get inside her memory. It's the fastest way to find Kuze.
这样太危险了
It's too dangerous.
而且是不负责任的做法
And highly irresponsible.
你确定
Are you sure?
有人恶意攻击就把我拉出来
You see any bad code headed my way, pull me out.
你怎么比我还紧张
How come you're the one sweating?
开始
Run it.
内部网路与少校连线 并予以解密
Cyber mind connection to the Major, now active...
启动深潜
and unencrypted
数据上传需要确认 请确认
consent required for data download.
我是蜜拉少校 我同意上传
My name is Major Mira Killian and I give my consent.
[怎么回事]
切断连线 把她拉出来
Disconnect. Get her out.
- 把她拉出来  - 我正在拉 她的大脑被入侵了
- Get her out!  - I'm trying, but she's being hacked.
快啊
Get her out now!
好了
Now!
你怎么样了
Are you okay?
我知道他在哪里了
I know where he is.
我知道那里 那是四眼帮的地盘
I know where he is. That's the four eye area
- 你在外面  - 好
- You're outside  - yes
我先进去看看 到时候再呼叫你们
I am advanced to see and call you again.
你们等我的消息
You wait for my news
每次都这样
Every time this way
我也是很厉害的 都没有表演的机会
I'm very strong, and there's no chance to perform.
门口两名守卫 有武装强化
Two mercs at the door. Armed and enhanced.
收到 交给我们处理
Copy that. We got it covered.
这家夜店藏有很多枪械武器
There's a lot of heat in here for a nightclub.
它是黑帮的堂口 你很意外吗
It's a Yakuza club. What did you expect?
我还蛮喜欢这里的
I quite like the place.
我怎么不觉得奇怪
Why doesn't that surprise me?
我去吸引他们的注意 看能不能到地下室去
I am gonna have to draw some attention. See if I can access the basement that way.
你不是来找麻烦的吧
You're not here looking for any trouble, are you?
我是来找姑娘的 顺便喝一杯
I am just here for the girls... and beer.
- 有事吗  - 我是来找人的
- Can I help you?  - I am looking for someone.
你以前来过吗
You've been here before?
我朋友在这里做过强化 专业的
My friend had some mech work done here.
我们这儿不做强化
We don't do mech work here.
不好意思
My mistake.
不如跟我们玩玩 找个人快乐一下
Why don't you come have fun with us? We will have some privacy.
我进来了
I'm in.
有需要通知我一声
I'll be here when you need me.
- 你朋友在这儿做过什么  - 我朋友在这儿做过强化
- You say your friend worked here?  - I said my friend had work done here.
你朋友
She's human?
他是人类
Your friend.
你这话是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
巴特
Batou.
你听到了吗
Can you hear me?
谁给你做了这身强化
Who did this stunning work on you?
真是完美
It is divine.
长得像鬼一样
Ladriya... guns.
给你
Here.
巴特 讯号都断了
Batou, I'm losing signal.
别紧张 亲爱的
Don't worry sweety.
没有人会来打扰我们
We have privacy.
听着
Listen.
这里收不到讯号
You know the signal is green in or out.
少校 我准备好了 你在哪里
Major, I'm in position. Do you copy?
啤酒
Beer.
到底怎么了 别让我担心
If you don't answer, you're gonna hurt my feelings.
拉卓雅 能联系上少校吗
Ladriya, do you have major on Comms?
没办法 讯号被切断了
Got nothing. The signal is still blocked.
我这个人没什么耐心 所以
I am afraid I get bored by that easily, so...
如果你不想说话
You don't wanna talk...
那就来跳舞吧
Maybe you wanna dance!
该死的 少校 你在哪里
Major, come on. Answer me.
我说过不找麻烦的
I thought you said no trouble.
跳啊
Dance!
等一下
Wait a minute
老实说
The truth is...
我不是跳舞机器人
I wasn't built to dance.
有讯号了 我去楼下的房间看看
Back on comms. I am heading to the back room.
想死你了 我马上过去找你
I missed you. I'll meet you there.
谁跟阪华机械同流合污 谁就得死
Collaborate with Hanka Robotics should be destroyed.
少校
Major?
我的眼睛
My eyes
巴特在哪里
Where is Batou?
在隔壁房间义体强化 他没事
In enhancement, next door. He is doing well
你承受了大部分冲击
you took most of the blast.
我只能眼睁睁的看着他
I saw him down there.
就好像
It was like...
他在等着我
He waited to see me.
我们给你做脑部扫描
We synaptic scanned you.
把你看到的东西送到中央实验室九区做分析
Everything you witnessed went to Section 9 to evaluate.
你知道 扫描的时候
You know, the scan...
出现了很多你的幻觉
Also turned up the number of glitches.
幻觉更多了
They've been getting worse.
什么时候开始
Since when?
自从我深潜以后
Since the deep dive.
那些幻觉会让你想起什么吗
Do any of the glitches mean something to you?
不
No.
想不起来
They don't.
你被拉进那个人用的液体里面
You have been inside the same shell as he has.
这可能会产生非常严重的后果
That could have very serious consequences.
你未经授权就深潜到艺妓体内
You were not authorized to deep dive the geisha.
我让你失望了
You're disappointed.
不 我是担心你
No, I'm worried.
你并非无懈可击
You're not invulnerable.
我能够修复你的身体 但保护不了你的大脑
I can repair your body, but I can't protect your mind.
为什么
Why not?
你可以看到我的想法
You can see all my thoughts so...
也应该可以保护它
You should be able to secure them.
你要明白你有多重要 蜜拉
Try and understand your importance Major.
总有一天所有人都会像你一样
You're what everyone will become one day.
你不知道这让我多孤单
You don't know how alone that makes me feel.
我能看到你 知道吗
I can see you out there, you know.
你看到几根手指头
How many fingers am I holding up?
幼稚
Funny.
说点好听的
Say something nice.
你装了电子眼
You chose those?
是工作需要
They are tactical.
- 一切都是工作  - 难道不是吗
- Always for the job.  - What else I got?
- 这眼睛适合你  - 是吗
- They suit you.  - Yeah?
我现在有夜视功能
I have night vision,...
和X光透视
and X-rays.
你能看到的 我也可以
I guess I see like you now.
别担心 你会习惯的
Don't worry, you'll get used to it.
谢谢你救了我
Thanks for saving my ass.
你没事就好
Glad to see you're okay...
少校
Major?
可以帮我喂一下狗吗
Could you feed the dogs for me?
我怕吓到它们
I don't want to scare them.
没问题
Anytime.
你觉得拨款太少吗 荒卷课长
Are you insufficiently funded, Mr. Aramaki?
还是公安九课需要更多的资源
Is section 9 missing some critical operational resource?
我们的需求都已经得到满足
We have everything that we require.
完好无伤的少校 才能发挥我们最大的战力
Major is our most sophisticated weapon only if she is intact.
欧莱特博士告诉我
And Dr. Ouelet informed me...
你让她深潜到损坏的艺妓里面找线索
That you let her dive a corrupted geisha.
你应该知道阪华机械公司
You realize there is a premium importance
是政府最重要的资产
that Hanka represents to this government.
而少校是我们公司的未来
Major is the is the future of my company.
如果你让她再一次受创
If you compromise your systems again...
我放把火把公安九课烧了
I will burn this section.
明白 社长
Yes sir.
卡特先生
Mr. Cutter.
你不要再威胁我
Be careful who is the threat.
我只对总理负责 你无权命令我
I am accountable to the Prime Minister, not to Hanka.
脸部义体强化 让你更美丽动人
Create your own beauty. Beauty enhanced.
你是人类
Are you human?
是的
Yeah.
把那些东西拿掉
Can you take that off?
让我看看你的脸
So I can see your face?
这是什么样的感觉
What is that feeling?
感觉
It feels...
很不一样
different.
你是什么
What are you?
[代号二五七一研究计划]
[阪华机器人档案]
看着我
Look at me.
阪华机械对我做了什么事
Tell me what they took from me.
对不起 他们没告诉我
I am sorry. They never told us.
用这双眼睛开车怪怪的
It feels weird driving with these eyes.
为什么吃药
Why do you take that?
让我的大脑不排斥我的身体
Um, keeps my brain from rejecting this body.
少校 巴特 你们赶快过来
Major, Batou, you need to get here.
发生什么事
What you got?
又有一位阪华机械的科学家被杀了
Another Hanka scientist has been found dead.
是达林博士
It's Dahlin.
马上到
Got it.
少校 这边
Major this way.
[代号二五七一研究计划]
这是什么
What is that?
她找到了九世从 奥斯蒙博士那里偷走的东西
She found what Kuze stole from Osmond.
是所有参与代号二五七一研究计划的人员名单
It's a list of everyone who worked on a project called 2571.
这就是他的目标
That's who he's targeting.
名单上还有什么人
Is there anyone else on that list?
[欧莱特博士]
找到她 快点
Find Oulet. Now!
她在路上 收不到讯号
She is in transit. Her comms are down.
我看着她 心里想着
I'm looking at her and thinking...
我要付你赡养费 和买小提琴的钱
"You want me to for pay for violin too".
你不要误会
Don't get me wrong.
我很爱我女儿的
I love that chick to pieces.
真的 她非常可爱
I do. She is amazing.
可是听她拉小提琴真是受罪啊
But when she prox that thing, it's painful right?
难道不能学钢琴吗
Why not piano?
反正学费都一样 就算弹得不怎么样
I mean, it's the same price, and doesn't sound so bad.
至少不会那么刺耳 对吧
At least if you can't play that proper, it sounds...
代号二五七一研究计划是什么
2-5-7-1! Tell me everything!
你真的不怕死 就为了二五七…
Are you prepare to die for 2-5-7...?
去
Go!
九世在哪里
Who is Kuze?
- 他为什么要杀欧莱特博士  - 我什么都不知道
- Why does he want to kill Ouelet?  - I don't know anything.
够了 够了
Enough, enough!
他还不能死
We need him alive.
拜托 我已经说过了
Please. I have been trough this.
你们抓错人了
You have the wrong guy.
那告诉我你是谁
So tell us who we do have.
我的名字叫 李·坎宁安
My name is Lee Cunningham.
- 你哪来的枪？ - 我不知道
- Where'd you get the weapons?  - I don't know.
谁把枪放在车上的
Who loaded the mines?
我真的不知道 我告诉你
I don't know anything about the weapons, alright I told you.
我正要去接我女儿 她去上小提琴课
I was picking up my daughter. She takes violin lessons.
你女儿叫什么名字
What's her name?
- 是她吗  - 对
- Is this her?  - Yeah.
她是不是很可爱
Isn't she a little angel?
- 这是你女儿  - 对的
- This is your daughter?  - Right.
你有孩子吗
Do you have that?
你住在哪里
Where do you live?
我不记得了
I can't remember.
好像是个很高的地方 是座高楼
I think it's a tall place. Is it a tall building?
是栋公寓大楼
It's a tall place, right?
你根本没有孩子
You don't have a child.
你也没有老婆 你一个人住 是个王老五
You have no wife. You live alone, It's just you.
什么 不
What? No.
那公寓根本没其他人
We went to your apartment.
你一个人在那里住了十年 不
You live there for 10 years by yourself.
- 所以你在说谎  - 我没有说谎
- So you're just lying.  - I'm not lying.
我没有杀过人
I didn't kill anyone!
你不说实话就别想离开 我没有
- Why do you keep doing this to me?  - Holocube disconnect.
拜托
Please!
真的不是我做的
I didn't do anything.
你们为什么一直问我同样的问题
Why do you keep saying this to me?
我不明白他怎么都不记得了
I don't understand. How can he not know?
大脑入侵需要创造真空 九世先删除他一段记忆
The hack must have created a vacuum. Kuze's wiped his memory...
才有真空写入假的记忆
and somehow installed a new reality.
至少他相信他有孩子
At least he got to believe he had a kid.
有什么区别呢
What's the difference huh?
幻想 现实
Fantasy, reality?
梦想 回忆
Dreams, memories?
其实都一样
It's all the same.
毫无意义
Just noise.
是他
It's him.
他来了
He is in there.
那里是封闭区域 他是怎么办到的 少校
This cube is secure. He can't be, Major.
测谎仪
Lie Detector.
一定是从那里入侵的
He must have hacked in that way.
赶快上传仪器的代码 追踪他的位置
We should uplink to the machine, trace the code, get a lock on his location.
快去
Do it.
别进去 太危险了
Don't go in there. It's too dangerous.
少校
Major
我们不知道他的能耐
We don't know what else he can do.
讯号不稳定 你能找到他吗
The signal is unstable. Can you get the lock on him?
我尽力 那开始吧
We gotta move fast. We're losing him.
连线中
Connecting.
你是谁
Who are you?
过来
Come here.
我很害羞
I'm shy.
我不像你这样
I'm not beautiful...
漂亮
like you.
告诉我你是谁
Tell me who you are.
我重生过不只一次了
I have been born more than once.
所以名字也不只一个
So I have more than one name
我会找到你
I'll find you.
我等着
Not yet.
事情还没完
I am not done.
正在追踪他的位置
The machine is tracing his location.
找到他了
We got a fix!
我没说谎
I need to see her.
请救救我
No Please. I know...what...
找到他了
We got him.
走吧
Let's go.
拿起武器
Weapons up.
- 走  - 上啊
- Go.  - On me.
趴下 趴下
Stay Down! Stay Down!
放下 放下
Put it down, put it down.
有炸弹
Grenade!
少校
Major!
回答我
Come in.
我知道为什么找不到他了
I knew why we could not find him.
他透过人脑布建自已的网路
He is using human minds to create a network of his own.
我们马上过去
We're coming to your position.
告诉我 你是谁
Tell me who you are.
我就是你要摧毁的目标
I'm that what you seek to destroy.
此生我的名字叫
In this life, my name is...
九世
Kuze.
你对我做了什么
What are you doing to me?
我把你连接到我自创的网络上
I have, connected you, to a network of my own creation.
当我死了以后
When I am finished in this world...
我的灵魂可以继续存在 然后重生
my ghost can survive there and regenerate.
你想对我怎么样
What do you want from me?
当你深潜到
I became...
艺妓机器人里面找我的时候
Fascinated with you...
我解读了你的代码
Reading your code...
然后就对你有了兴趣
when you were inside that geisha.
你给了我前所未有 但又似曾相识
Like nothing I had felt before, yet so...
熟悉的感觉
Familiar.
我们是一样的
We are the same.
我们不一样
We are not the same.
你滥杀无辜
You kill innocent people.
无辜 你说他们无辜
Innocent? Is that the...what you call them?
他们把我害成这样
I am as they need me.
是谁害你的
Who made you?
他们是怎么跟你说的
What have they told you?
说你是第一个
That you were the first?
第一个有灵魂的人脑机器人
The first cerebral salvage.
我们的失败 让他们吸取了教训
You were born of lessons...
造就了你
from my failure.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
他们支解我的身体 像垃圾般丢掉
I was conscious while they dismembered my body,
当时我还有意识
and discarded me like garbage.
我躺在手术台上
I was lying on a table...
医生说我的大脑 跟他们制造的液体不相容
Listening to doctors talk about how my mind had not matched with the shell that they had built.
我就是代号二五七一研究计划
I'm projected to 2571...
失败的案例
had failed...
然而他们还不死心
and they had to move on...
直到制造了你
to you.
你真完美
Morning beauty you are.
看来经过了我们的失败
They have improved us so much...
让他们颇有收获
since they made me.
他们认为我们是人类进化的缩影
They thought that we would be a part of their evolution.
但我们这两件作品
But they have created us...
却超越了他们
to evolve alone...
我进化了
beyond them.
进化 这就是你的想法
Evolution? That's what you call?
杀光所有害你变成这样的人
Killing everyone who made you?
你根本就没听懂
You are not listening to me.
你是杀人凶手
You are murderer.
是他们先要杀我的
They tried to kill me first.
我是自我防卫
It is self-defense.
保护我自已
The defense of self.
还会死更多人
More will die...
直到我查清楚
until they tell me...
他们对我做了什么
what they took.
我绝不允许
I won't let that happen.
你想杀了我吗
You want to kill me?
像其他人一样
Like everyone else.
那就来吧
Do it, then.
这就是你存在的意义吗
Do what you are programmed to do.
那是什么
What is that?
我不记得了 它本来就在那里
I kick in to remember, but I am haunted by it.
你也是吗
Do You see it?
德古沙
Togusa!
不要吃他们拿给你的药物
Don't take the medication that they gave you...
那个药物会抑制你的记忆
They use it to suppress your memories.
你的躯壳属于他们 但灵魂不是
Your shell belongs to them, but not your ghost.
你的灵魂属于你自已
Your ghost is yours.
记住我的话
Remember that...
或许你会想起所有的事情
and maybe you can remember it all.
离她远一点 把枪放下
Get away from her! Get down on the ground now.
少校
Major...
Major!
哦 蜜拉
Oh Mela
我的天啊 你没事
My God, you're all right
我们都很担心你
We're all worried about you
你跑去哪里了
Where are you going
别这样
Don't do like that
拜托
Please.
你们究竟对我做了什么
What did you do to me
不管九世跟你说了什么 或是你看到了什么
No matter what you say to nine or what you see
我从来都不曾想要伤害你
I never wanted to hurt you
多少个人
How many?
很多
Dozens
多少
How many?
在你之前 我们失败了九十八次
98 unsuccessful attempts before you.
你杀了九十八个无辜的人
You killed 98 innocent people.
不 我没杀过任何人
No, I didn't kill anyone.
没有那些失败
You wouldn't be here.
没有那些实验 你现在也不会站在这里
You would not exist if it weren't for those experiments.
那些实验
Experiments?
- 我是你的实验品  - 不
- Is that what I am to you?  - No!
不 蜜拉
No, Mira!
牺牲是必须的
Sacrifices were made.
实验体是从哪里来的
Where did the bodies come from?
我是从哪里来的
Where did I come from?
你是卡特先生找来的
Mr. Cutter brought them to us.
我没有问过他
I did not ask questions.
港口呢
The harbor.
我的父母
My parents.
他们的死因
The way they died.
是真的吗
Did that happen?
不
No.
那是我们给你创造的假记忆
We gave you false memories.
当卡特先生要把你指派到公安九课
Cutter wanted to motivate you.
打击恐怖分子 我没同意
To fight terrorists. I didn't approve.
这太残忍了 可是我的工作很重要
It was cruel, but my work, that was important, and...
所以你诞生了
you were born.
你是这么的完美
You were so beautiful.
我的一切都是假的
Nothing I have is real.
我找到他了
I found him.
我说过你要当心
I told you to be careful.
你知不知道他是谁
You knew who he was the whole time.
你制造了他
You built him.
他是一个
He had a...
极端暴力又不稳定
Violent unstable mind.
他的大脑和液体连接并不相容
His cerebral connection wouldn't hold!
- 我试过救他  - 不
- I tried to save him!  - No.
你让他自生自灭
You left him to die.
没有九世的踪迹 我去搜查上城区
Nothing on Kuze yet, sir. Checking upper zones next.
少校有消息吗
Is there any word on Major?
她不在网路上 断线了
She's gone. Off-grid. Silent.
收到 课长
Copy that, sir.
我知道她去哪里
I know where to find her.
我没叫你过来
I didn't ask you to come here.
你是没叫我
You never ask.
可是我每次都来
But I always do.
他们派你来找我吗
Did they send you to bring me in?
我是来钓鱼的 有看到鱼吗
I'm just here to fish. Did you see any?
你一向服从命令 如果他们派你来杀我呢
You are a company man, you follow orders. So, if they ordered you to kill me.
别跟我胡说八道 我会生气的
Stop saying shit like that. You're gonna piss me off.
水下怎么样
What's it like down there?
又冷又黑
It's Cold and dark.
好像是另一个世界
Just a million miles away.
没有声音
No voices.
没有数据流
No data streaming.
什么
Just...
都没有
nothing.
- 很可怕  - 那你为什么下水
- It scares me.  - Then Why do you do it?
它感觉很真实
It feels real.
为什么不拦住九世
Why didn't you stop him?
我不知道还能信任谁
I don't know who to trust anymore.
你信我 不是吗
You trust me, right?
我信你
Yes I do.
我只是不喜欢那样
I just don't like it.
我要你带我回去
I need you to take me back.
还有很多事要查清楚
There is more I need to find out.
好吧
Sure.
欧莱特博士
Dr. Ouelet...
你给她说了什么
What have you told her?
她知道了
She knows.
我派人去抓她
I'm bringing her in.
保安队呼叫总部
Hanka security to Headquarters.
发现少校
We have the Major.
为什么给她打镇静剂
Why is she sedated?
她被恐怖分子策反了
She's been turned by a terrorist.
但你已经知道了
But you know that already.
她去找你的时候 你就应该通知我的
You should have called the first time she came to see you.
而你却告诉她所有的事情
Instead, you gave her information.
你凭什么觉得你有权利…
What makes you think you have the...
- 她的作为宣告了  - 二五七一研究计划的失败
- Right to tell me that?  - 2-5-7-1 took us close.
而现在是进入下一阶段的时候
It's time to move on to the next iteration.
二五七一研究计划没有失败
2-5-7-1 is not a failure.
我会删除她的记忆 并重新编码
I will delete all the data and reprogram her.
- 她不会记得这些事的  - 不…
- She won't remember him at all.  - No, no, no, no.
你把恐怖分子的数据下载后
You download all the data on the terrorist...
就要终止她的程式 将她关机
and then I order you to terminate.
- 什么  - 你会做出更好的
- What?  - We'll build one that's better.
- 我会删除她的记忆  - 没有用的
- I'll delete everything.  - You deleted before.
- 她是我的  - 不
- She's mine.  - No.
你和我有合约协议
She is a contract... with me.
我们成功了
We succeeded.
她胜过人类 也胜过机器人
She is more than human... and more than AI.
我们改变了她的躯体 但她的灵魂还在
We change her entire identity. But her ghost survived!
这就是导致我们失败的原因
Her ghost is what failed us.
我们控制不了她 所以她已经没有价值了
We can not control her. She is no longer a viable asset.
这将是你对她做的最后一件事
You should be the one to do it.
你要对我做什么
What are you doing to me?
给你进行脑波扫描
I'll run the standard synaptic.
下载恐怖分子的数据
Upload your data on the raid.
看看九世到底跟你说了什么
I'll find out exactly what Kuze told you.
你知道他说了什么
You know what he told me.
真相
The truth.
你要删除我的记忆是吗
You're deleting everything, aren't you?
不
No.
所以我也会不记得
So I don't remember...
你
You.
我是蜜拉·凯莉恩少校
My name is Major Mira Killian...
我不同意你删除这些数据
And I do not consent to the deletion of this data.
我不同意删除
I do not consent.
我们不需要你同意
We never needed your consent.
不需要任何人同意
Yours or anyone's.
你要杀了我
You're killing me...
是不是
Right you...?
蜜拉
Mira?
你能听到吗
Do you hear me?
蜜拉
Mira?
这是你真实的过去 拿着它
This is your past, your real past. Take it.
- 警卫  - 快走快走
- Guards!  - Come on, come on!
快点走
Come on, go!
走
Go!
走啊
安全警报在二十五楼
Security alert on level 25.
现在启动封锁程序
Initiating Lockdown procedure.
请前往指定的避难室
Please relocate to your designated safe room.
谢谢你的合作
Thank you for your cooperation.
这就是人心带来的问题
That's the problem with the human heart.
我要扫描看她在哪里
I want to see her scan.
她杀了欧莱特博士
She killed Dr. Ouelet.
你不能再找她了 阪华机械的保安队正在抓她
You are to have no further contact with her. Hanka security will hunt her from here.
- 你下了什么命令  - 格杀勿论
- What are the orders?  - To terminate on sight.
你想杀了她 是你制造了她
You want to kill her? You built her!
- 让你的手下退下  - 少校不可能杀欧莱特博士
- Have your sergeant stand down.  - The Major would never hurt Dr. Oulete.
她现在已经不是少校了
She is not the major anymore!
九课的人员被恐怖分子策反控制
We have a section 9 operative under terrorist programming.
这件事要是传出去 你们就完了
This goes public your unit goes down.
你想杀她
You kill her...
必须先杀了我们
You kill us.
我会好好考虑你们的意见
I'll take that under advice.
现在怎么办
So what now?
[素子故乡]
喔 小南瓜
Oh, the puppy.
喔 你吓了我一跳
Oh, you surprised me.
它喜欢你
She likes you.
我要找…
I was looking for...
进来吧
No, come in.
来 快进来
Yeah, go, come come.
- 你喝茶吗  - 好的
- Can I offer you some tea?  - Okay.
那是素子的房间
That... Motoko's room.
我女儿一年前去世了
My daughter died a year ago.
对不起
I am Sorry.
她离家出走
She run away.
那孩子比较叛逆
She was a difficult.
我们常吵架
We fought.
但我想父母跟孩子那能不吵架的
But I guess we all fight with our parents, right?
请坐在这边
Please come on the sit.
她怎么死的
What happened to your her?
我不知道
I don't know.
政府的人把她的骨灰送回来
The ministry sent me her ashes, and...
他们说我的女儿自杀了
They told me she took her own life.
可是素子 不…
But Motoko... No, no, no.
我不相信他们
I never believe them.
她过得很开心
She was happy...
跟一群朋友住在不法之地
living in the lawless zone with her friends.
而且到处跟别人说
She'd write her manifestos about...
科技的发展到最后
how technology was...
会毁灭这个世界
destroying the world.
然后有一天
Then one day...
警察来了
the police came...
他们就跑了
and they run.
真奇怪
It's strange.
我在很多女孩身上看到了她的身影
I see her in so many young women.
在大街上 在我梦中
On the street, in my dreams.
就好像她还活着
As if she is still here.
素子她…
She was...
很勇敢
fearless.
无所畏惧
And wild.
你让我想起了她
You remind me of her.
对不起
Sorry.
我什么地方让你想起她
Why do I remind you of her?
是你看我的眼神
The way you look at me.
你到底是谁
Who are you?
我不知道
I don't know.
等等 等一下
Wait, wait, wait!
你还会再来看我吗
Will you come again to visit me?
我会的
I will.
荒卷课长
Aramaki.
你听我说
Listen to me.
根本就没有恐怖袭击
I was never in a terrorist bombing.
我的父母
My parents...
一切都是他们植入的虚假记忆
Everything was data they installed in my mind.
而且还有其他像我这样逃家的人
And there were others. Run-aways like me...
都被他们抓去做人体实验
considered disposable.
九世就是其中之一 所以他要找阪华机械
Kuze was one of them. That's why he's coming.
复仇
To Hanka.
你有什么证据
Can you prove this?
欧莱特博士可以做证
Dr. Ouelet can.
欧莱特博士已经死了
Ouelet's dead.
卡特社长说是你杀了她
Cutter says you killed her.
把我放上网路 我要引出九世
Put me on the grid. I need Kuze to find me.
这样卡特就会知道你的位置
We will be exposed to Cutter.
我知道 但我必须这样做
I know, but I have to do this.
我要和总理会面
I'm going to meet with the Prime Minister.
必须让卡特收手
He must be stopped.
病毒已经扩散了
The virus has spread.
呼叫九课的队员 监视网路通讯
All agents stick to mental comms.
别找兔子…来杀狐狸送死
Don't send a rabbit... to kill a fox.
我们被盯上了
We are burned.
重覆
I repeat.
我们被盯上了
We are burned.
报告社长 已掌握少校行踪
We have located Major on the grid.
她在不法之地
She's in the lawless zone.
空中支援在五分钟后抵达
Air support 5 minutes out.
蜘蛛坦克能否赶到现场
Is the spider tank within range?
可以 等候社长指示
Yes sir. Awaiting your orders sir.
素子
Motoko!
它真的存在
It is real.
这个地方
This place.
我想起卡特他们
I remember what they did to us.
对我们所做的事 他们来这里抓走了我们
Cutter and his men. This is where they took us from.
我们以前都在这里玩
We used to sleep right here.
我们就像一家人
We were like a family.
一群逃家的人
All of us run away.
除了彼此
We had nothing...
我们一无所有
except each other.
可是连这个也被夺走了
They took that from us.
你的名字叫秀雄
Your name was Hideo.
素子
Motoko.
这是你的名字
That was your name.
素子
Motoko.
跟我走吧
Come with me...
在我的网路王国
my network.
我们会进化 超越所有的人
We will evolve beyond them.
我们一起让那些人 偿还我们所受的苦
And together we can avenge what they have done to us.
来吧
Come...
跟我走
with me.
我要从这里手动遥控
I will take control from here.
展开武器系统清单
Weapons system manual command.
启动蜘蛛坦克
Spider tank now active
是卡特 他发现我们了
It's Cutter! He found us!
目标已锁定
Target acquired
不
No!
目标已摧毁
Target eliminated.
你差点就赢了
You came close...
怪物
you freak.
机电系统短路
Motor center compromised.
空中支援到了吗
Sniper team on site?
快到了 社长
Approaching the target now sir.
跟我来吧
Come with me.
这里没有我们的容身之处
There is no place for us here.
不
No.
我不能离开这里
I'm not ready to leave.
我属于这里
I belong here.
我会永远和你在一起
I'll always be there with you...
在你的灵魂深处
your ghost.
已经锁定目标
Target is in view.
那你还等什么
What are you waiting for?
开枪
Do it!
不
No!
继续射击
Keep firing.
斋藤 你找到少校了吗 她没事吧
Saito, have you found Major? Is she safe?
她会没事的
She will be.
嘿
Hey...
Hey.
说点好听的
Say something nice.
你叫什么
What's your name?
荒卷告诉我 你之前有个名字
Aramaki told me you had a name from before.
我叫素子
Motoko.
我们的少校并没有离开 对吧
Major still in there, right?
是的
I am.
卡特社长
Mr. Cutter.
我和总理谈过
I talked with the Prime Minister.
你被指控谋杀平民与叛国罪行
You are accused of murder and crimes against the state.
我就知道会是你
I thought that it might be you.
拒捕将就地正法
It is unwise to resist.
别杀我
Please.
少校
Major?
对于卡特社长
I am with Cutter.
你有什么要对他说 在杀他之前
Do you wanna say anything before I kill him?
告诉他这就是正义
Tell him this is justice.
就是我存在的意义
It's what I was built for.
请确认就地正法
So do you give consent?
我是少校
My name is Major.
我同意你把他删除
And I give my consent.
[草薙素子]
你以后不用再来这里了
You don't have to come here anymore.
我知道
I know.
我的心属于人类
My mind is human.
但身体却是机械做的
My body is manufactured.
我是第一个全身义体化人脑机器人
I am the first of my kind, but...
但不会是最后一个
I won't be the last.
我们执着于记忆 觉得它定义了我们
We cling to memories as if they define us.
但定义我们的是我们的行为
But what we do defines us.
我的灵魂活着 提醒未来的义体化机器人
My ghost survived to remind the next of us...
人性才是我们的美德
that humanity is our virtue.
我知道我是谁
I know who I am...
我要做什么
and what I'm here to do.
少校
Major.
目标已确认
Engage targets.
授权你 攻击
You're authorized.